♬ 光と闇の水面
吸い込まれてゆく
Seven years have passed, it is now 1888.
-1888, London East End-
♬ 引き合うように 重なる波紋
It is a time when women were being victimized by the mysterious serial killer known as Jack the Ripper.
♬～
He would come to be known as "The Terror of our Times."
♬ 誇りの道を往く者に
太陽の導きを
But another "Terror of our Times" was born that year as well...
Born from the battle between Jojo and Dio!
♬ 野望の果てを目指す者に
生け贄を
♬～
♬ 震えるほど心
燃え尽きるほど熱く
Sora koboreochita futatsu no hoshi ga
Two stars fall from the sky
♬ その手から放て 鼓動
Original Translation:
Mudasubs
Hikari to yami no minamo suikomareteyuku
One shining in the light, the other sinking into darkness
♬ 身体 漲る勇気で
♬ 迷いなき覚悟に喝采を
Hikiau you ni kasanaru hamon
A ripple drawing the two of them together
♬ その血の運命 ジョジョ
Quality Check:
Tonitonichopchop
Hokori no michi wo yuku mono ni taiyou no michibiki wo
One will walk the path of pride and receive the sun's guidance
♬～
Yabou no hate wo mezasu mono ni
One will walk the path of unbridled ambition...
Ikenie wo
Demanding sacrifice!
Furueru hodo kokoro moetsukiru hodo atsuku
Let that burning in your soul calm the trembling of your heart
Timing/Typesetting/Encoding:
Fadeout4
Sono te kara hanate kodou
Strike down your fears,
Karada minagiru yuuki de
With courage coursing through your veins!
Mayou naki kakugo ni kassai wo
You cannot overcome your pain unless you can accept...
Sono chi no sadame
The legacy of your bloodline!
Jojo!
http://www.some-stuffs.com/
Episode 2: "A Letter from The Past"
(実況)取った～！
He's got the ball!
The ball has been stolen by the hero of Hugh Hudson Academy!
(実況)ボールを奪い取ったのは
我がヒュー･ハドソン校の雄！➡
Jonathan Joestar!
ジョナサン･ジョースターだ！
(ｼﾞｮﾅｻﾝ)うお～‼
Jonathan Joestar, normally a mild-mannered gentleman, towers over his opponents at 6'4"!
(実況)普段は 静かなる男！➡
身長195cm
ジョナサン･ジョースター｡➡
At this moment however, he's roaring as he charges towards the goal!
雄たけびを上げて
ゴールへ 突進する！➡
Will he be able to win the championship for his team as the match draws to a close?!
卒業目前の この試合
優勝で飾れるか!?
(選手１)うお～っ！
(実況)お～っと 捕まった！
He's been tackled!
But... but he's still standing!
(実況)が！ 倒れない！
Two more opponents are closing in!
(選手２･選手３)うお～！
(実況)また２人！➡
They're on him! He's pinned down!
捕まった！ ３人！
ぬお～！
This is incredible!
(実況)すご～い！➡
The three men that attempted to tackle him are now being dragged along towards the goal line!
３人に タックルされたまま
引きずりながらも➡
突進をやめない！
なんというパワー！
なんという根性！
What power! What determination! My god, he's like a locomotive!
まるで 重機関車です！➡
(選手４)てや～っ！
あ～ ４人目！
And now there's four!
This is too much, even for Joestar!
(実況)さすがに ぐらついた！
ふんっ！
うお～っ！
There's a pass!
(実況)あ～っ！ パスが！
(実況)通った！
飛び出したのは…｡
It's received...
And it was caught by...
(実況)ディオ～！
やはり 我が校の ﾃﾞｨｵ･ﾌﾞﾗﾝﾄﾞｰです！
Dio! The pass was caught by Dio Brando!
(選手５･選手６)でや～っ！➡
ぐえっ！
Can he make it past them?!
(実況)抜けるか？➡
He does! And again...!
抜ける！ 抜ける！➡
抜けた！➡
And he's through!
He's on a solo run to victory! Once again, his speed is unmatched!
単独走です｡ 華麗だ！
相変わらず 華麗な走りっぷり！➡
トラーイ！
It's a try!
(観客たち)うお～！
(実況)やった～！➡
They pulled it off!
This final match of the season secures the championship!
最後の試合を
優勝で飾りました！➡
It was all thanks to the excellent teamwork between Jojo and Dio!
ジョジョとディオ
絶妙のコンビネーション｡➡
ぴったり合った 呼吸｡
We did it, Jojo!
(ﾃﾞｨｵ)やったな ジョジョ！
Dio, your running was even more amazing than usual!
ディオ！
見事だったよ 君の走りは｡
Thank you.
ありがとう｡ だが ジョジョ
君あっての トライさ｡
But I couldn't have done it without you, Jojo.
Dio Brando is on track to graduate at the very top of his class.
(実況)ﾃﾞｨｵ･ﾌﾞﾗﾝﾄﾞｰは 法律で
ﾅﾝﾊﾞｰﾜﾝの成績で 卒業する予定｡➡
片や ジョナサン･ジョースターは
考古学の分野で➡
Meanwhile, his partner Jonathan Joestar has been making waves in the field of Archeology!
見事な論文を 発表しています｡➡
Victory wouldn't have been possible without these two young men! They are the pride of the entire university!
この試合も
この２人あっての優勝｡➡
我が校の誇りです！
Jojo, we should tell father about our victory as soon as we get home.
ジョジョ この勝利を 早速
お父さんに 報告しなくちゃあな｡
うん｡
Even after being adopted into our family, since when has Dio referred to my father as his own?
《ディオが 正式な養子になり
僕の父を➡
｢お父さん｣と呼ぶようになって
どのくらい たっただろう？➡
In spite of the conversation we just had, I feel no friendliness between the two of us...
今 ディオと
あんな会話をしていたけど➡
正直 僕は 彼に対して
友情を感じていない｡➡
Why? He's so charismatic, so affable...
なぜ!? 彼は あんなに すごくて
いいやつなのに》
《まだ ７年前の事件を疑惑し
恐怖している！》
Those events from seven years ago are still causing me doubt and confusion!
Dio! The school paper wants to do a story on your friendship. Could you give a us statement, please?
(男性１)ディオ！ 学園の新聞に
君たちの友情について 書くけど➡
話してくれないか？
友情だって？ てれるな｡
Our friendship? How embarrassing...
Come on! We'd love to hear it.
(男性２)
頼むよ｡ 僕らも聞きたいな｡
ん～ じゃあ…｡
Well in that case...
《ふん！ 友情だと？➡
Friendship?! Spare me your idyllic drivel, you undignified pieces of filth!
きれい事を並べて
にこにこするなよな｡➡
クズどもが！➡
もうすぐ 卒業｡➡
Soon, I will graduate... and then I will no longer require Lord Joestar's support!
もはや ジョースター卿の
援助は 要らん！➡
７年 ジョジョと
表向き仲良くしたのは➡
I've spent the last seven years fabricating a rapport with Jojo, all for this moment...
この期を待ったから！➡
My plan is to become the sole heir to the Joestar fortune!
計画は ジョースター家の財産を
乗っ取ることさ｡➡
財産を法的に
自由にできる年齢になった！》
And I am finally of age to rightfully claim that fortune and use it as I see fit!
(ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰ卿)ゴホッ ゴホッゴホッ｡
お父さん ご気分はいかがですか？
Father, how are you feeling?
(ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰ卿)うむ だいぶ いいよ｡
ただ せきが止まらないな ゴホッ｡
A little better... aside from the cough.
The doctors recommended I be admitted to the hospital today.
今日 医者に
入院を勧められたよ｡
The hospital? That's a terrible idea!
入院？
それは しない方がいいですね｡
The level of care at a hospital is atrocious, their only concern is how much money they make!
病院は 施設が悪いくせに
もうけることばかり考えて➡
入院を 勧めているんです｡
うむ 私も断ったよ｡
I turned them down, I feel more at ease in my own home.
自分の家の方が
安心していられる｡➡
And besides, the pain in my chest is gone, and the swelling in my hands seems to have gone away...
胸の痛みも なくなったし➡
指の腫れも 引いたみたいだ｡
良くなってる｡
I'm already feeling better.
《風邪を こじらせただけなのに
こんなに 悪くなって》
All he did was catch a cold...
But he's in such horrible condition...
ところで ディオ ジョジョ
優勝おめでとう｡
Now then, Dio, Jojo... congratulations on the championship!
えっ!? もう 知ってるんですか？
You already heard about it?!
大学の友人が さっき来て
教えてくれたよ｡
A friend of mine from the university informed me about it.
That's an awful friend you have there!
ひどい友人をお持ちです！
We came home as soon as we could to surprise you with the good news!
喜ぶ顔が見たくて
すっ飛んで 帰ってきたのに！
アハハハッ…｡
Ah. Regardless, I am quite pleased!
いやいや 喜んどる｡
私は 鼻が高いよ｡
I'm so proud of both of you. I have such wonderful sons.
素晴らしい 息子たちだ｡
I'm particularly proud of all you've accomplished, Dio.
ディオ 君は 特に頑張った｡
卒業したら
なりたいものになるがいい｡➡
Once you graduate, I want you to pursue whatever path you'd like.
You will have my full financial support.  You are family, after all.
援助は 惜しまない｡
君は 私の家族なんだからね｡
You have my deepest gratitude for giving me the chance to rise above my meager upbringing...
貧しい出身の この僕に➡
チャンスを与えてくれて
ありがとうございます｡
I will do my best to live up to your expectations.
ますます 励みたいと思います｡
This is a secret that only I know...
《僕だけが知る 秘密｡➡
この仮面を作った者は➡
I can only wonder what purpose this mask was created for...
一体 何を目的として
製作したのだろう？➡
Part of my interest in it is rooted in the fact that my late mother was the one who acquired it...
そして 何よりも 覚えていない
亡き母が買った物という➡
思慕の情もある》
Perhaps one day I can publish my studies on the secret behind the mask...
《いつか この仮面の秘密を解いて
発表し➡
Wouldn't it be amazing if I became renowned for my work?
センセーションを
巻き起こせればいいな》
あっ！ しまった！
Oh, drat!
I appreciate the help as always, Master Dio.
(執事)
いつも助かります ディオ様｡
ああ｡
(執事)年ですな｡➡
It must be my age... going up the stairs is becoming quite a trial.
階段を上るのが
結構 苦になりました｡
I just thought of something... truly dreadful!
僕は 今！ とても
恐ろしい想像をしている！
Dio...
《ディオは…》
He's...
Dio!
ディオ！
Just now...
今 その薬 どうした？
What did you do with that medicine?!
What ever do you mean?
｢どうした｣とは？
Do you usually bring my father his medicine?
君は いつも 父さんに
薬を運んでいたのかい？
ああ それが？
Yes. What of it?
７年前 君のお父さんが出した手紙
偶然 見つけたよ｡ 読もう｡
I found the letter that your father sent, seven years ago...
"I have fallen gravely ill..."
｢私は 今 病にあります｡
多分 死ぬでしょう｡➡
"I'm going to die soon, I can tell..."
分かるのです｡
病名は 分かりませんが➡
"I don't recognize this disease, but my chest aches, my hands are swollen, and I can't stop coughing..."
心臓が痛み 指が腫れ
せきが止まりません｣｡
These symptoms are the same as my father's!
この症状
僕の父さんと 同じ症状だ！
一体 これは どういうことだ!?
ディオ！
What is the meaning of this, Dio?!
君は 一体 何が言いたい？
What exactly are you insinuating?
Let me see that medicine!
その薬 調べさせてもらおう｡
ジョジョ
その薬を調べるということは➡
Jojo, if you doubt the validity of that medicine...
我々の友情を疑うこと｡
Then you doubt our very friendship...
友情を失うぞ！
Is that worth risking our friendship?!
《うっ！ ディオの目に威圧されて
目を伏せてしまった｡➡
The intensity of Dio's glare made me avert my eyes...
あくまで 疑惑に過ぎず➡
I don't even have any real evidence to base my accusation on, only suspicion.
僕の心にも
確信が まるでないからだ》
Jojo... place the medicine back on the tray...
ジョジョ
その薬を 盆の上に戻せよ｡
Do that, and I will ignore your preposterous accusation.
そしたら 君のバカげた
考えのことは 忘れよう｡
ううっ…｡
Dio! Swear to me...
ディオ！
紳士として 君の実の父➡
As a gentleman, swear on the honor of your father and the Brando name!
ブランドー氏の 名誉に懸けて
誓ってくれ！ 自分の潔白を！
Then I will trust you!
If you can swear on the honor of your true father, then I will return the medicine and never speak of this again!
自分の父親に誓えるなら
僕は この薬を 盆の上に戻し➡
二度と この話はしない！
If my suspicions are correct, then no matter how prideful he is, he wouldn't swear on such a lie.
《もし 僕の推理どおりなら➡
彼の誇りに対する性格から
誓いは できないはずだ！》
Dio, swear this to me!
ディオ さあ 誓ってくれ！
S-Swear?
ち… 誓いか｡ ぐぐ…｡
あ… あいつの名誉に 誓うだと？
You want me to swear on his honor?!
勘違いするな！
Who do you think he was...
There was nothing honorable at all about that pile of gutter trash!
あんなクズに
名誉などあるものか‼
You've confirmed my suspicions, Dio.
君への疑惑が 確信に変わったぞ
ディオ！
君の動揺と憎悪は 普通じゃない｡
Your lack of composure and your malice are not normal.
I don't know what happened between you and your father...
君と 実の父親の間に
何があったのかは知らんが➡
But whatever it was, it drove you to murder him!
君は 父親を殺害している！
くっ…｡
I will protect my father, and the Joestar name!
僕は 父を！
ジョースター家を守る！
ぐあっ！
や… 殺るか｡
So, you want to fight?
ディオ！
君の７年間の考えが 分かった！
Dio, I know what you've been after these past seven years!
There was never any friendship between us!
僕らには 最初から
友情など 存在しなかった！
そして 父には もう近づけん！
And you will stay away from my father!
この薬を分析して 必ず
刑務所に 放り込んでやるぞ！
I'll have this medicine examined, and I'll see you pay for your crimes!
《くそっ！ あと一歩という
ところだったのに｡➡
Damn it...
And I was so close...
Was stumbling upon that letter some kind of divine justice?!
手紙など見つかったのは
何かの前兆か？》
No! I won't let my plans be ruined because of that piece of trash!
《いや あんなクズのせいで
計画を潰して たまるものか！》
(ﾀﾞﾘｵ)《死んだ女の服なんぞ
売っ払え‼》
Get rid of that dead bint's clothes already!
《母は 苦労して死んだ！➡
He put my mother through hell before she died...
Just the thought of that oaf's blood running through my veins is enough to drive me mad!
あいつの血が この体に
流れていると思うだけで➡
Booze, bring me my damn booze!
気が狂いそうになる！》
《もう 引くことはできない！》
But now... there is no turning back!
Father, I'm going to London for a few days.
父さん 僕は ２～３日
ロンドンに行ってきます｡
Until I get back, please accept treatment from these doctors, and no one else.
その間 この医師たち以外からの
手当てや 薬は➡
一切 受け取らないでください｡
The master has lost faith in our care...
私どもの看護じゃ
信用できないんで？
That is not the case, but please do as Jojo asks.
(ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰ卿)
いや ジョジョの思っているとおり
させてやってくれ｡
I may not understand his reasons, but I have faith in my son...
何の理由があってか 分からんが
わしは 息子を信じるよ｡
ゴホッゴホッ｡
F-Father...
と… 父さん｡
His condition is getting worse...
《病状が 悪くなっている》
He may need some sort of antidote...
《解毒剤が
必要なのかもしれない》
It will take him at least three days for him to track down the source of that poison...
薬の証拠をつかむのに
３日と見た！
That leaves me three days to take care of Jojo...
３日の間に
ジョジョを 何とか始末せねば！
And to make sure none of the evidence points to me!
それも
完全犯罪でなくては ならん！
Seven years ago, my blood caused a reaction in this mask.
７年前 この仮面は
俺の血で 作動した｡
If I can cause those spines to penetrate Jojo's skull, he'll be dead in an instant!
この骨針が ジョジョの脳みそに
食い込めば 間違いなく 即死！
It will appear to be an accident during his research!
しかも 研究中の事故死となり➡
No one will ever suspect foul play!
殺人容疑は
俺には かかってこない！
Jojo... it looks like your curiosity...
ジョジョ！ お前の研究で
お前自身が死ぬんだ！
-2 days later, London-
Is going to be the death of you!
(御者)どうどう｡
Whoa there!
《大学の研究室でも
薬の分析は 不可能だった｡➡
The university's laboratory was unable to identify the components of the poison...
Which means it more than likely came from the Orient.
そうすると 東洋の薬である
可能性が強い｡ となると…》
That means...
Young Master!
(御者)旦那 こっから先は
オウガーストリートって➡
You're approaching Ogre Street, the most dangerous slum in all of London!
ロンドンでも
一番 ヤバい街なんでさ｡
I know... but I must go, nonetheless.
分かってるよ｡ だけど 僕には➡
行かなくてはならない
理由がある！
君は
引き揚げてくれてかまわない｡
You're free to leave.
《ディオは
ロンドンに住んでいた｡➡
Dio lived in London...
東洋の薬を手に入れるとしたら
ここしかない｡➡
This is the most likely place for him to have found such an exotic poison...
入手先を見つけて
証拠と 解毒剤を》
Once I track down its source...
I'll have my antidote and my evidence!
また 行き止まりだ｡
Yet another dead end?
んっ？
(猫の鳴き声)
うっ ひどい！
猫が 子犬を食ってた！
How dreadful! That cat was eating a puppy!
≪(口笛)
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)おい刺青！ 任せるぜ｡
(刺青)ああ！
Hey, Tattoo! Take him out!
Got it!
We'll carve up that fancy tosser and leave him dead in the alley!
あの身なりのいい
あんちゃんの肌を 切り刻んで➡
身ぐるみ 剥いじまいな！
I see... this place really lives up to its name!
なるほど 名前に ふさわしい街だ｡
(刺青)うきあああああ！
(刺青)ニヒヒッ｡➡
うへぇ～！ こいつ バカか!?➡
Is he stupid?! He caught my bloody knife with his bare hand!
ナイフを
素手で 止めやがった！➡
ヘヘヘッ だがよ
おいらが このナイフを➡
I guess you weren't thinking, because if I twist this knife then you'll be missing four fingers!
ちょいと引っ張ったら
指 ４本は そげ落ちるぜ！
Just try it!
試してみろ！
And the moment you do, you'll receive a kick in the bollocks from a leg the size of a tree trunk!
引っ張った瞬間 僕の丸太のような
足蹴りが 君の股間を潰す｡
I have a cause that's worth losing some fingers over!
僕には 指４本など
失ってもいい 理由がある！
それは 父を守るため！
家を守るため！
I will defend my father... I will defend my family...
I have more at stake in this fight than you do!
君らとは
戦う動機の格が 違うんだ！
(東洋人)アチャーッ！
そこの 東洋人｡
君なら知っているな｡
You there, you're of Asian descent...
Do you know of a place that sells poisons from the Orient?
東洋の毒薬を売っている店を｡
You!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)お前！
You say you don't mind losing your fingers?
指４本 失うぐらい
平気と言ったな!?
あぁ～ん？
Let's hope you're not bluffing, rich boy!
ハッタリぬかすなよ｡
金持ちのアマちゃん！
試してやる！
We'll put you to the test!
I won't let anything stand in my way!
どんな妨害があろうとも
突き止めるのみ！
What's with this dunce?!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)何だ こいつは!?
ケンカのド素人だ！➡
Have you ever been in a real fight?!
You're protecting your head, but the rest of you is wide open!
頭部以外
全部 隙だらけだぜぇ～ッ‼
おおっ!?
ハハーッ！ 刃が 骨まで達した音｡
That's the sound of steel cutting into bone!
ナイフのせいで
狙った胴には 行かなかったが➡
You may have spared your head by throwing that knife, but you still took a direct hit!
まともに 食らったな！
えっ!?
うぐっ！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
《げぶっ！ な… 何てやつだ！➡
W-Who the hell is this guy?!
ハ… ハッタリじゃあねえ！
こいつには 指どころか➡
H-He wasn't bluffing!
He's not just willing to lose his fingers, he doesn't even care if he loses his legs!
両足だって失ってもいい
覚悟がある！➡
そして 恐怖や痛みに耐える
精神力がある！➡
He's got the determination to cast aside all fear and physical pain!
I should have never tried to pick a fight with a tough guy like this!
やめりゃよかった｡➡
こんなタフガイに
ケンカ 吹っかけるのはよぉ…｡》
What? Jojo went into Ogre Street on his own?
何？ ジョジョが１人で
オウガーストリートに入ったと？
(御者)お止めしたんですが…｡
I tried to reason with him, but...
心配かけるといけない｡
Let's not cause any unnecessary worry. Do not speak of this to Lord Joestar.
ジョースター卿には
黙ってるんだ｡
へい｡
《仮面で始末する手間が
省けたな｡➡
Looks like I may not have to use that mask after all...
Has he been murdered already? Perhaps a lynching?
既に 殺されたか
野たれ死んだか》
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)や… やめろ！
D-Don't...
With my honor as a Speedwagon at stake, I refuse to forgive you if you lay a hand on this gentleman!
その紳士に 手を出すことは
この スピードワゴンが 許さねえ｡
Gentleman?
｢紳士｣？
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)１つ 聞きてえ！➡
Tell me something...
Why did you hold back when you kicked me?
なぜ 思いっ切り
蹴りを入れなかった？➡
With those legs, you could have smashed my face in!
あんたの その足ならよ➡
俺の顔を メチャメチャに
できたはずなのによ｡
僕は 父のために ここに来た｡
だから 蹴る瞬間➡
I am here for the sake of my father.
The moment before I kicked you, I thought of your own father, your mother, your siblings...
君にも 父や母や
兄弟がいるはずだと思った｡
I don't want to bring any pain upon your father, as well...
君の父親が悲しむことは
したくない！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)《こいつ… マジか!?➡
He's... he's serious!
He's naive to his core!
限りなく 甘っちょろいやつだぜ！
しかし…》
But...
I see... My friends aren't hurt very badly either...
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)《なるほどな…
仲間も 大したケガじゃない｡➡
こいつは 正真正銘
精神的にも 紳士だ｡➡
This chap's a true gentleman, right through to his heart of hearts!
Truly worth of my admiration!
気に入ったぜ！》
So, what's your name?
あんたの名前を 聞かせてくれ｡
Jonathan Joestar.
ジョナサン･ジョースター｡
All right then, Jonathan Joestar...
よし ジョナサン･ジョースター｡
You said you were looking for a proprietor of Oriental poisons, correct?
東洋の毒薬を売るやつを
捜していると言ったな！
I'd be careful! He's a cunning bastard!
気を付けな｡
ヤツは こすずるいぜ！
(医者)もう ３日…
ジョジョ君 帰ってきませんなぁ｡
It's been three days... and Jojo still isn't back.
He'll accomplish what he set out to do.
言ったことは 実行する子だ｡
昔は ちょっと 頼りなかったが
成長されましたな｡
He was rambunctious when he was younger, but he's grown into a fine man.
I fear I may have been too strict with him in order to achieve that...
そのために
必要以上に 厳しくしたものだが｡
(猫の鳴き声)
Damn it... Jojo, you had better be dead by now...
《くそっ ジョジョのやつ｡➡
きっちり
野たれ死んだんだろうな!?➡
Did he discover where the poison came from...?
まさか 薬の証拠を…！》
《酒‼ 飲まずにはいられない！➡
How could I lower myself to drink this swill...
あのクズのような父親と
同じことをしている！ くそっ！》
I'm heading down the same path as that booze-addled piece of trash!
D-Damn it!
(男性１)
ウッヒッヒッヒ｡ ウヒヒッ｡
(男性１)気を付けろィ！
Oy, watch where yer' goin'! You clumsy fop!
どこ見て 歩いてんだ!?
この トンチキが！
Oy mate, I think the little shrimp got some piss on me jacket when he nudged me!
おい相棒！ 俺の上着に
あのガキの 小便の染みが➡
付いてねえか 見てくれ！
(男性２)ハハハッ！
こら 聞いてんのか!?
ケツの青い ガキがよ！
You listening, you little son-of-a-bitch?!
(男性１)うげっ！
Me teef! Me fuckin' teef!
(男性２)ああ… この野郎
よくも 俺のダチ公を！
You bastard... what have you done to my friend?!
ほぉ～ 衛生観念もない
虫けら同然の クズのじじいが➡
I'm amazed a disgusting, senile old fool like you has the nerve to speak to me in such a way!
よくも このディオに
そんな口が利けたものだ！
面白い！ いい機会だ｡
This should be interesting...
I can use this opportunity...
To test this out before I use it on Jojo!
ジョジョの前に
まず ここで試してやる！
何を ゴチャゴチャ
言ってるんでい‼
What're you yammerin' about?!
Consider this a live experiment!
人体実験だ！
(男性１)あ… あひ｡
あひっ！ あひあひ…｡➡
ぐぇっ！
うあ！ こ… この光は 一体!?
W-Where is this light coming from?!
幻覚か？ 今の光は…｡
Was it just my imagination?
So he's dead?
死んだか｡ 面白くもない｡
How humdrum! It's just a run of the mill torture device.
ただの 拷問殺人道具よ｡
It can't be...
まさか…｡
He's not dead?!
死んでいない！
W-What in the hell is he?!
な… 何だ？ 一体 こいつは!?
くわっ！
Fangs?!
牙！
ウシャアアアッ！
《うげ～っ！
な… 何だ!? このパワーは!?》
What... what incredible power!
うう…｡ くっ｡
He's... he's still standing?!
《ま… まだ来る！➡
あいつ 腕の痛みは
感じないのか!?》
Doesn't he feel the pain from his arm?!
H-He barely grazed me, but my collarbone is broken!
《かすっただけなのに
鎖骨が砕けている！》
《川に… 飛び降りるのだ！》
I have to jump into the river...
はっ！
うっ！
う… うあああああっ‼
か… 渇く｡
I thirst...
I don't know why, but I'm so incredibly thirsty...
何か知らねえがよ…
渇いて 渇いて しょうがねえんだ｡
《血が… 吸い取られてる！》
He's draining my blood?!
What the?!
《何…!?》
Now I understand the secret behind the mask... but...
《石仮面の秘密が 分かってきた｡
し… しかし…》
ぐわあああっ！
ちぐしょ～！
Damn it all! I don't want this sunrise to be the last thing I see!
あの太陽が 最後に
見るものだなんて 嫌だ～‼
ぎゃああああああ～！
た… 太陽の光｡
T-The sunlight...
Where are the servants? Why are all the lights out?!
どうした!? 執事｡
なぜ 邸内の明かりを消している!?
ジョジョ！
Jojo...
I found what I was searching for, Dio!
とうとう つかんだぞ ディオ｡
君の 悪魔のような
陰謀の証拠を！
And now I have proof of your devilish conspiracy!
なっ!?
♬(ｴﾝﾃﾞｨﾝｸﾞﾃｰﾏ)
I'll be the roundabout
♬ I'll be the roundabout
The words will make you out 'n' out
♬ The words
will make you out'n'out
I'll spend the day your way
♬ I spend the day away
Call it morning driving through the sound and
♬ Call it morning
driving through
♬ the sound and
in and out the valley
In and out the valley
♬～
The music dance and sing
♬ The music dance and sing
They make the children really ring
♬ They make
the children really ring
I'll spend the day your way
♬ Spend the day away
Call it morning driving through the sound and
♬ Call it morning
driving through
♬ the sound and
in and out the valley
In and out the valley
In and around the lake
♬ In and around the lake
Mountains come out of the sky
♬ Mountains come out of
the sky and they stand there
and they stand there
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
♬ One mile over we'll be there
and we'll see you
♬ Ten true summers
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
♬ we'll be there
and laughing too
Twenty-four before my love you'll see I'll be
♬ Twenty four before
my love you'll see
♬ I'll be there with you
There with you
Next Episode
Jojo... I realize it's selfish, but I have one last request...
I can tell from his scent! He reeks worse than the lowest gutter trash I've ever met!
I'm through with being a mere mortal, Jojo!
Dio!
Episode 3:
"My Childhood With Dio"
ジョジョ 勝手だけど 頼みがある｡
最後の頼みだ｡
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)においで分かる｡➡
ゲロ以下の においが
プンプンするぜ！
俺は 人間をやめるぞ！
ジョジョ！
ディオ～！